Add such deals on Bajaj Finance or Bajaj Finserv. The market
may fluctuate again, but you should not panic.
I had urged you yesterday also, when the
market was in a long correction, to
go with a little buying. Today I will
say this, you should understand a little here, but
whatever opportunity there is, it is a buying opportunity. You have to
buy Reliance, buy Title,
buy Relax. If you add such deals, one
day you will see that you are in a big profit from this
and you are going to get a big profit. The
market is very good and the
market will be very good in the times to come as well. You have to remain
courageous, remain courageous, stay focused. You have to
invest only in very good companies. You have to
share very thoughtfully.
And when you clear it, then see your full
responsibility. I am telling you about my problem in PIMS.
In banking, those five gems,
my five gems,
which I have given you from Infosys and TCS, you can
also add the training system from ITI to it.
You can also add Indiamart Intermesh, you
can also add Diction Technology.  You
can add the last one also, all these
are great, vibrant and excellent companies and
here it is today, it is very underrated like
I consider HDFC to be very underrated, I
consider Reliance to be very underrated, I
consider Asian Paints to be very underrated, I consider About
India to be very underrated, I consider it to be very
underrated, I consider Actual to be
very underrated and the history sheet which is
my very dear Nihara and is like my child
's share, it seems the yearning for it is about to start, keep
out and buy ITC and HUL also, stay in the market, stay in the market,
you will get the benefit of staying in the market, so
see if it breaks